{
    "subject": "resource/Shuttle_America",
    "predicate": "property/website",
    "object": "http://www.shuttleamerica.com",
    "human_readable": "The website of Shuttle America is www.shuttleamerica.com.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9444978833198547,
            "question": "Which website belongs to Shuttle America?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9409247040748596,
            "question": "What is the website address for Shuttle America?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9354054927825928,
            "question": "What is the web address for Shuttle America's official site?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9312938451766968,
            "question": "Can you provide the URL of Shuttle America's website?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9284587502479553,
            "question": "What is the address of the official Shuttle America website?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9242646098136902,
            "question": "What is the URL for Shuttle America's website?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9049971699714661,
            "question": "How do you access the official website of Shuttle America?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8935428261756897,
            "question": "Where can you find information about Shuttle America online?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7530291676521301,
            "question": "Where can you find information about Shuttle America's services and schedules online?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6765848994255066,
            "question": "If you want to learn more about Shuttle America, where should you go online?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The website of Shuttle America is www.shuttleamerica.com.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4752_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you find information about Shuttle America's services and schedules online?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4752_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you find information about Shuttle America online?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4752_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How do you access the official website of Shuttle America?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4752_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4752_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4752_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4752_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4752_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4752_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4752_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4752_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4752_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4752_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4752_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe documents mention \"Wikipedia: en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shuttle_America\" and \"Website: www.shuttleamerica.com\", which indicates that the website of Shuttle America is indeed www.shuttleamerica.com."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe context information provided includes the website for Shuttle America, which is listed as `www.shuttleamerica.com`. Therefore, the statement \"The website of Shuttle America is www.shuttleamerica.com\" is supported by the given documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}